<para fontSize="12" alignment="justify">
<b>WMBR</b> is a registered service mark of the Technology Broadcasting Corporation.
</para>
<para alignment="center" spaceBefore="10" spaceAfter="6" fontSize="18">“RULES OF THE LOGS”</para>
Questions on these rules should be referred to the Chief Engineer.
<ol fontSize="12">
  <li> The engineer signed into the logs is referred to as the OTA Engineer (this person is referred to as the “Transmitter Duty Operator” by the FCC).  Engineers must sign in with their full, legal name.  The OTA Engineer is responsible for making sure that all entries in the log, made during his or her shift, are made completely and accurately.  She or he must initial EVERY log entry made during their shift, including entries made by other people.</li>
  <li> Please print clearly, with a black or blue ball-point pen.</li>
  <li> Times may be specified in 12 or 24 hour notation, provided 12 hour times are qualified by “a” for AM or “p” for PM.  Write the actual time above the pre-printed time where applicable.</li>
  <li>Reception of EAS Alerts should be noted in the margin of the Operating Log.</li>
  <li> Changes in Forward Power should be noted in the margin of the Operating log and a new set of transmitter readings should be taken immediately after making the change.</li>
  <li> If any Burk readings cannot be adjusted to within their prescribed limits, you must contact the WMBR Emergency Technical Staff IMMEDIATELY.  If you cannot reach one of them, YOU MUST SIGN OFF.</li>
  <li> If the Tower Lights are observed to be off when they should be on (when it is dark out), you must call the Logan Airport Tower (FAA) at 617-561-1919 and tell them.  WMBR’s tower is located at 60 Wadsworth St. in Cambridge.  The coordinates of the tower are 42 degrees 21’ 42.0” North Latitude, and 71 degrees 5’ 3.0” West Longitude.  The top of the tower is 357 feet (109 meters) above ground level, and 367 feet (112 meters) above sea level.  The FCC Tower Registration Number is 1007726.  Get the name of the FAA person who took the call.  Write this person’s name in the log, along with the time, date, and the words, “Tower Light Failure”.  Someone from the Emergency Technical Staff should then be contacted immediately.</li>
  <li> WMBR measures its power via the “direct” method.  To calculate the forward power via the “indirect method”, multiply the PA voltage times the PA current times 0.66 (our Power Effeciency Factor).  Divide this number by 240 watts (our nominal transmitter power) to get a percentage.</li>
  <li> Actions or items not done shall be crossed out with a single stroke, and initialed (and dated if necessary).  All corrections, including those made at a later date, must be initialed by the original engineer who was signed in at the time.  Old logs are kept in the office closet for a minimum of two years.  If you are advised that you made a log entry mistake, please correct it as soon as possible.</li>
</ol>
<para alignment="3" spaceBefore="24" spaceAfter="12" fontSize="15">The Emergency Technical Staff:</para>
